Hello everyone!
And Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Merry Feast!
Shakishaki!
That's right, today we're having a Christmas gift exchange!
Too peaceful.
Did everyone bring a present?
It's just like Bakaselver!
The presents that everyone prepared are placed over there so that no one can see what's inside.
But since it's not worth it to just exchange them as usual...
So we're going to play a game of touch, and the winner can choose who will receive the gift from whom.
The cashier asked me, "What kind of games do you play there? and
What game do you want to play?
We'll play a game with these blocks, and then we'll decide who wins.
It's cute.
We're all going to play for fools.
The winner gets to choose a gift.
But you don't know what's inside. You don't know if it's someone from Iapew.
You only know if it's a gift from someone else, so people can choose what they want.
I see... let's go ahead with the numbers.
A cake...
There's cakes and stuff, but only the stuff I like.
Let's go to the front of the opening.
Arul!
I'm on it. - Actually, it's a present.
Two...
I'm doing it...
Export colo...
Preerst, get a star.
I'm going to get it.
Sign
儿
It's an agreement.
What? Two 8th places in a row is not good enough for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Then it's over.
I don't want to take it.
Then you're really risking your life.
I was really hyped up for it.
I was really into it, but now I'm going to hand them out.
But I'm surprised.
But I was surprised. I didn't expect it to go down this much.
But I might be the one who's really screwed up. - Really?
Who only has 3 cards?
What?
I can see my Christmas present.
Oh, shit. So we'll play rock, paper, scissors to see who wins?
Yes, sir.
First one gets a "goo" rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
You want to play rock-paper-scissors-scissors?
Whoa.
First, let's play "go, rock, paper, scissors".
Shall we draw?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Here you go.
Pull? He pulled, I'll pull.
What, you don't want me to look at it? No, no, no, no.
They're getting fewer and fewer. That's right.
Does she have a joker? Because there's one that's a little bit out.
What? Think.
It doesn't line up.
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
It's a mistake.
Oh, yeah!
Yes!
Here you go.
Pow.
What? It's going up.
What? Is that possible?
What? Wait, my nose is running.
Yeah, it's going up.
What? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Yes! Yeah!
Wait a minute!
How is this possible?
Too strong!
Let's see...
Dick!
I'm going bacco!
I'll turn into a bucko!
This girl scares me.
Of the three of you, one of you has feelings for the other.
I don't have feelings for her.
That's great.
With four people, it's all credits.
You're only showing one.
There it is!
Pull it back, dickhead.
No, I want my present.
Wait a minute.
If we show our dicks, they'll pull us out.
They'll know.
I don't have it.
You don't have it?
Oh, no!
I don't have it!
You don't have it?
Oh my God!
We're in a fight.
That's right.
Kana's leaving.
Hang in there.
If there's one more...
Shioi loses.
Yes, you lose.
Please...
You mean I've been eating all night?
It's obvious from the start.
Hmm? That's what I thought.
That's scary.
First place goes to Meru.
Hitomi comes in second.
Third place goes to Hana.
Yay!
I can choose from the building ten.
Please stop talking about everyone else!
We did our best to make the switch.
I'm sure you've all made up your minds.
The three of us will talk it over once and decide on a number.
What's yours? One, two, three.
Turn around.
Oh, but, Mr. Spafe...
Spafe, to all of you.
I'm sorry.
Okay, that's it. Here we go.
Four... four... three...
Three.
I like it. I like this way of deciding.
I like the way you're going with it. I'm going to get dashed.
That's good.
Follow me.
I'll follow the same rules.
Okay, then.
First place, Miru's
Yay!
You mean Hitomi's staff, right? Yes.
Staff's, please.
What's this?
What? Where's mine?
But you know, for the next episode.
Yeah, I was wondering if you could save it for the next episode.
That's great... a present for everyone.
There's always next time, so don't be shy.
Don't be shy.
Okay, so...
I'll go ahead and open Chi-chan's present.
Oh!
What?
For you?
What's this?
A Span warmer?
Electronic body warmer.
Electronic body warmers are awesome.
This is great.
Thank God.
That's about right.
Thank you.
Already, right?
There was another one.
Oh, wow.
What? Wait a minute.
Loin dai broth birth.
Saul.
Ehhhh...
Wow!
Something Haruna Kojima's
I made it.
I did.
It's so good!
I'm looking forward to taking a bath!
Poka-poka set!
It's nice!
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
From me?
From Mil-chan.
From Mil...
This is for you.
What's this?
It's a head scrub.
Thank you.
We... we... we get our hair done at work.
You know, when we get our hair all stiffened up from work.
With this, it comes off in an instant.
What?
Savon.
We smell the same.
Thanks for matching.
Yay!
Have a scrub.
Thank you so much.
I'll keep you company.
What is it? It's so light.
What?
It's hot!
Oh, my God!
That's great.
I'm so happy for you.
I didn't tell you.
It's me.
I just bought Mario Kart at Mario Wonder.
I just bought Mario Kart at Mario Wonder, and now I want to buy Daitetsu.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Thank you very much.
It's so hot, I'm so happy.
One more time.
There's always next time.
I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it, Shiori-chan.
Don't worry, I promise.
No wonder I'll be back a lot.
We'll warm up together then.
It's hard to get warm.
I told you earlier, I won't go out to the bath.
We can't take a bath together. I'm sorry.
He ate something.
We can't take a bath together.
So, let's go to the second round.
Yes, sir.
I thought you wanted cake.
I do.
After we're done?
Can I just have a strawberry then?
Isn't that the best?
It'll be fine.
She'll be fine.
This one?
Then you can have this one and this one.
While Ogi-chan works hard.
Shiori wanted to eat, too.
Let's eat, Shiori.
Joker, don't eat it.
Joker, go away.
I won't.
Thank you.
That's how it's looking right now.
I think we've got a pretty good balance this time.
All right, let's see what you got.
rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors?
Yes, let's play rock, paper, scissors.
I'll draw first.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Let's go!
Poi!
Why can't I get this one? Wait a minute.
That's Shibayu's move.
Oh, isn't that a good pace?
I'd be worried if my friends were here.
I don't know.
I couldn't get mine to line up.
Why did you do it?
You're so cool.
I don't know. It's easy to draw.
You're scary.
Right?
Don't say weird things.
Sorry, sorry. I got it!
Hey, scary!
What are you holding up?
I see... I don't draw from you.
I don't get it.
So cute!
Ah, Furumaru-chan!
Furu-chan's strong!
Furu-chan's strong.
Hello.
What?
Huh?
Why?
Why? Christmas.
I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe that's why.
Keep saying that.
That's so sweet.
It's just... It's just...
It's so hard to keep up.
What?
Oh, wow.
Wow.
But, two more, three more?
If it were Chi-chan, no, for sure.
Then I'll write it.
What? It's like a "ba-ba-ba-bon".
I'll take the middle one.
Oh, no, that's right.
Can I ask you something?
I'm scared.
What? No lineup? Then Okon and Chi-chan will take it.
Then, this way...
I'll have Chi-chan for the rest of my life.
What? What? That's one!
Over there? That way, everyone.
But I don't know if it's a regular card.
Take a picture.
Don't take it.
I have to.
Pow! Pow!
Congratulations.
Good for you.
Wow.
Let's have a look.
All right.
Let me see.
Oh, wow.
Okay, I'll mix it up.
I'll start here.
Well, I don't know about you, but I'm going to have to ask you to pull it for me.
Okay.
You don't see it?
I don't see you.
I don't see it. - Yes, you do.
Then the middle one.
Yes, yes, yes.
You lost. Yes, sir.
The Joker doesn't move. He's not moving.
He was there from the beginning. He was there from the beginning. He was there from the beginning.
What are you doing?
I don't know, I lost.
Order, number one, number two, number three, number four...
It felt good, didn't it?
It felt good. Good, good.
Let's start with Miru-chan.
I wonder how Ogi-chan and Hee-chan are doing. The staff has theirs.
What's the next present?
I'll open it first.
I wonder...
Another Peach Bowl?
No, this little one.
What?
Charalin.
Oh, my God!
What?
Delivery for 5,000 yen.
Yum!
Oh, wait! It's so good!
I didn't even know this existed.
I'm pretty sure I've never seen it before.
Christmas.
We're...
We're having a Christmas party.
Oh, you're not listening!
Maybe we'll have the party here.
Oh, my gosh! Yay!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Okay, here you go. When you get inside Hane-chan...
You can already see it.
What's this?
There's no such thing.
This is, um...
You're going to wear it.
So don't open it now.
Huh!
Oh!
Have a good day!
Looking forward to it.
Yes, ma'am.
Curly, curly, curly.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I'm done using it.
I'm off.
Bye!
I want to go.
Can I open this one first?
Are you sure? He's going to get changed.
He's so cute.
Good for him.
Wait, that's the worst part.
He's so excited when I take it off.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's so cute.
It's so cute.
So cute.
Everyone's in the middle of Christmas.
Isn't it amazing? This one.
It's adorable.
It's so cute.
But they do it like this.
It's warm.
I'm sweating.
What?
Come back for a story.
I'll talk to you later.
Thank you. Thank you.
He's cute.
He's so cute.
Baby.
And the back.
Oh, my God.
That's so cute.
It looks great on you.
It looks good on you.
And the color.
Chelle.
Much better.
It looks good on you.
Wait a minute.
This one.
It's so cute.
We're gonna put Abi in this and go home.
It's really cute.
Too cute.
Seriously.
So cute.
Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
So...
Oh, no.
Look at that!
Planetarium
Planetarium!
I'm so happy about the planetarium.
I've always wanted a planetarium.
originally
I wanted this, let's go for it!
I see.
No, it's nice.
It's got a search function, and it's got Bluetooth.
Can you make phone calls with it?
Yes, it does.
It says you can play music on it.
Can I get another one?
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Yay, yay.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, I don't have mine.
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't seem to have any more.
I see... I wanted to buy Shinagi's. It's fine.
It's cute.
Everyone liked it so much they bought it.
When I got in the box, Chi-chan was exchanging gifts.
Isn't it so cute?
It was a wonderful project.
It was fun to have a fun Christmas gift exchange like this with everyone.
So, I hope you all have a wonderful Christmas.
That's all for not.e.co.ru Mii.
Bye bye.
Material to play
methodology